All right, welcome everyone
to Office Hour of CS6300
Subway Development Process,
and here's Paola and Will.
Hi, everyone.
So, let me see, today's
February 18, and students are
watching, are supposed to
watch P3L3 design patterns.
which definitely helps
with group project
deliverable one so this week
we only have one assignment
group project d1 so it's
um gets yeah students
just um get familiar
with a team member and
start working on d1 right
and for now i don't see
any questions yet on it.
So probably we can use this
time to see if we have anything
new in the industry
or in the academia
community regarding the
software development
process, given how fast
the industry is changing.
so i have i have i'm
reporting on something
i ordered and i'm i
was at an event to
where people were
reporting some studies and
there was this very
interesting study on
feedback on when
you use agents in
software engineering
development teams
and so they were studying
the good the bad and the
ugly right and it was pretty
interesting and to see you
know where you where they
are very good and where
they're bad but then i ask
a question and and we don't
have answer to some things
yet so for instance they ask
a question so there are
things in which are really
terrible and so and so that
triggered my question in
um so something they're
very bad in correcting their
own code right and and so I
was asking do we know anything
about maintainability
right like you know you
write this code and you have
pieces of this code that are
written by agents so what
do you and of course they
know nothing yet but the
initial study on correction
they make you think that
they will be terrible and so
it was funny because the
presenter at the end say so
if you're thinking to fire
all your employees don't
do it I mean it's it's
comforting we are really very
much needed nice so we do
have a question now but I'm
also wondering when you
talk about the good the bad
and the ugly I'm clearly
ugly which one of you is the
good and which is the bad no
it was not about the three
of us okay it's not about
the three of us there is
a first question there shen
okay so first question um
the instruction for hpd1
please say that feedback from
a zero will defeat the
purpose of team interaction
for some of us who are
completely new even after
team intelligence is
applied and we come up with
a design that is better
than all of our individuals
design how do we know
that we will be building
the app correctly. Little
concerns that we will
go down the rabbit hole
of errorless assumptions
or incorrect software
design that we
cannot easily get out
of in later weeks.
I mean literally we have
a list of requirements
in assignment 5
already so as long as
students and groups
following those
eight or nine
requirements. I think in
my experience in
the past five years,
no team has the veer
off if they just
follow those eight
or nine requirements.
I think the hard
part is to get that
requirement in the first
place, which is not
scalable in an online
format like this.
So to short answer, I don't see
a lot of concerns right there.
But I also want to get
Paula here to talk more
about the way we are designing
the group project right
now. apparently we already
have the engineer the
the requirements up front
right um do you think
is whether it is viable to
have um that part as part
of the group project as
well maybe not in an online
format or maybe not in a
repeatable group project because
we kind of reuse this group
projects every semester
right but then if we have
to let the students to do um
hands-on requirement
engineering maybe every semester
we have to find a new kind
of a hack or something and
not a repeatable uh group
project assignment like we
do right now so paula yeah
i think if if uh if the
this the requirements come
from the students right then
the project can go really
in every direction it's also
much more difficult to say
in a setting if you know
to evaluate requirements i
would take they would take
a much larger part of you
of your course because when
you build your requirements
you you don't build them
just from documents or
materials so the the setting of
playoff would be much much
more complicated so you
should imagine a complete
different setting and um i
could imagine an hackathon
in in in in other classes if
you teach just requirements
or the first part until
design and and you stop
there then you have much more
time and you can simulate
something at the beginning I
mean I actually can imagine
in the future even in online
setting though to have
and and they exist really
like some LLM pretending to
be your customer to try to
get the requirements but
then if you have your every
group has different requirements
then the project will
diverge completely because
uh in this way right like
if you have the requirements
as a base and you're sure
as she was saying that you
cover the requirements uh
and you work with your team
you kind of you don't get
much of feedback but you
are still covering the
requirements you are you're
simulating actual interaction
like in in real life And so
I think for a course that
tried to cover the old
software development lifecycle,
this is the way to go.
Thank you, Paula.
Let me see how we answer
the first question.
um it's quite um it's
quite quiet um today
is it the spring break
coming soon or what
it could be i don't
know i don't know in
other states but in
most of the county
around atlanta children
are home from school
so some parents might
also be overwhelmed
I'm saying this, I'm
just like completely
hearing the noise
in the other room.
So Paula, you are
from Italy, right?
I know that Italy
is a long country.
In Italy,
is there any part of the
country that has a kind of
spring break and they do the
spring skiing kind i'm saying
no we don't we don't do it
so there is the so spring
break is not a thing in italy
right so we so i i never
the the term spring break
before coming to the united
states in italy all the
vacation are associated to
some other event so um so
we do what do we do during
summer we do carnival in
February and usually everybody
that let's say the cutoff
maybe is Tuscany everybody
in northern Tuscany goes to
go skiing and but it's but
carnival was in February so
it's still winter and people
in the south if they're
really passionate because in
the south so you know in
Italy it's all crossed by
mountains right so the
mountains where people usually
ski are the one at the border
and northern border so this
is what i'm saying and they
are also the tallest ones
so there is no more often
um but and then easter is
usually like end of march
beginning of april and so
again people in the north might
still get away with knowing
the whisking especially
if they go up in the alps
um but then it's more and
then people in the south
actually in sicily in in april
might be able to go to the
beach already it's a small
country but we have it all
including the food
i wanted to finish
my advertisement
for the country
right so it seems that
we have no more questions
for the team uh for the
time being i think the
the team is busy
communicating get get to know
each other so um i think
we can call it uh call it
early then we can um
revisit the next next week
to see if people have
more questions especially
given the um more
assignment instruction
uh it's uh yeah this
is coming and also
for more questions
about Alessa, right?
So yeah, thank you
all. And I will
let Paula and Will say goodbye.
So long, everyone.
Bye, everybody.
Have a great week.
We'll see you next week.
Bye, all. Thank you.